http://www.topshareware.com/info/privacy_policy.aspx

Free Downloads > Privacy Policy
Our site is advertiser supported to bring you free content. For this reason, TopShareware.com
(as do many other sites) tracks user traffic patterns generally throughout the site.
This helps us to better understand what pages our site visitors are viewing most
while on our site so we can continue to improve our site content. TopShareware.com
also furnishes our advertisers with some of this broad demographic data. This information
is essential to advertisers and is important so that we can keep our content free.
It is our policy not to sell, or share the names, addresses or private contact information
of any of our customers with third parties. If you have questions about how one
of our advertisers uses information about you when you click their ad and go to
their content, please contact them directly or visit their web sites for more information.
Shopping on TopShareware.com is a currently a service offered by a third party business
and commerce partner "Digital River." Digital River is a trusted brand on the internet
and all e-commerce transactions conducted through this service are conducted through
industry-accepted secure methods.
Use of Cookies
Advertisements served by Google, as a third party vendor,
use DART
cookies. These cookies are used to serve ads based on your visit to this
site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART
cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Cookies are very common on the
internet. They are small, inoccuous text files that websites use to remember certain
information, or preferences, that you provide. This information is saved on "your"
computer's hard drive as a unique id that identifies your browser (not you) when
you visit a site that uses cookies. A cookie file can contain information that is
useful to site operators for a variety of reasons that serve both the customer and
visitor. It may store items like your user ID or other personal information that
you supply. A cookie can not read data on your hard disk or read information in
cookie files created by other sites. Cookies can be turned off in your browser,
but doing so may limit your ability to participate in certain activities provided
by a site.
Cookies are commonly used
in online shopping baskets. Patrons of our shopping services presented by Digital
River will be presented with a single cookie. Digital River's cookies are used only
to identify the customer, not to identify any specific customer traits. This allows
them to maintain consistency in the shopping basket and enable a more pleasant shopping
experience. Click here for the Digital River Privacy Statement.
TopShareware.com
may make available to site visitors a way to voluntarily register with this site
for a better visitor experience or to sign up for products, services or improved
personalization features. We will update our privacy policy about the nature of
the information we track before making those services generally available.
Audio : Games : Desktop : Business : Internet : Multimedia : Software Developer : Utilities : Web Developer : Screensavers© 2002-2020 TopShareware.com. Legal Disclaimer | Privacy Policy
